At Seabrook High, it's Zoms vs. Poms
Z-O-M-B-I-E-S is a fantasy, comedy, romance film directed by Paul Hoen.
Two star-crossed freshmen – a zombie, Zed and a cheerleader, Addison – each outsiders in their unique ways, befriend each other and work
together to show their high school and the Seabrook community what they can achieve when they embrace their differences.
Addison, played by Meg Donnelly.
Zed, played by Milo Manheim.
Bucky, played by Trevor Tordjman.
Eliza, played by Kylee Russell.
Bree, played by Carla Jeffery.
Zoey, played by Kingston Foster.
The film explores themes of high school, cheerleader, musical, zombie, curious.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.